The essence of balance is detachment.
To embrace a cause, to grow fond or spiteful,
is to lose one's balance,
after which, no action can be trusted.
Our burden is not for the dependent of spirit.
-- Mayar, Third Keeper
I was a, kid.
No parents, no home...
Running messages and picking pockets to keep...
...my ribs from meeting my spine.
One night I saw a man.
Folks just passed him by like he wasn't there.
I thought he must have something valuable, so I snuck up on him and made a grab.
- That's not for you.
- Please, sir, I'm hungry.
Don't tell the Hammers. I promise--.
- What is your name, boy?
- Garrett.
- You have talent, lad.
- Let go of me, old man!
- To see a Keeper is not an easy thing,
...especially one who does not wish to be seen.
We have a need for those as gifted as yourself.
If you've grown tired of how you live, then follow me,
...and we will show you a different way.
- Leave me alone!
- As you wish.
I caught up with him just before he vanished into the crowd..
It was the beginning of a very long education.