The most promising acolyte left us,
not out of the lesser folly of sentiment,
but the greater folly of anger.
His heart was clouded, and his balance was lost,
but his abilities were unmatched.
Even then, we knew to watch him most carefully.
-- Keeper Annals
I have a simple job planned for this evening.
Break into a guarded mansion,
steal another fat nobleman's priceless trinket,
and leave quietly.
Lord Bafford is out of town,
and rumour has it that the captain of his house guard went with him, as a bodyguard.
The time is ripe for a bit of burglary.
The front gate of Lord Bafford's manor is always guarded,
and the main street is far too exposed.
But Cutty tells me there's a better way in,
around to the side, more 'out of the way'.
One guard, and likely no
witnesses to...
...complicate matters.
The piece Cutty wants is a sceptre:
silver, jewels...the usual adornments.
It should command a high price.
Bafford, like most of his kind,
probably keeps his treasures on the top floor of the place,
close to his heart, and far from his servants.
No point in waiting.
I have Cutty's old sketches of the place,
and everyone who's going to be asleep inside already is.
It's time to begin.