Before death came,
the liars were made to feast...
upon the hands of the thieves,
and the thieves were made to ingest...
the tongues of their liar brothers,
and we praised the Master Builder for his judgements.
--The Hammer Book of Tenets
I went to Cutty's place to deliver the scepter,
but Cutty wasn't there.
He'd been arrested by the Hammerites.
Apparently they didn't approve of his occupation,
and I doubt they approve of mine.
So hopefully they'll never catch sight of me
when I break him out of their prison. Which is what I'm going to do.
They're holding Cutty in a mining complex carved out of a quarry.
The quarry's flooded, but the Hammers
still work the top level mines,
and have converted part of the complex into a penitentiary for those who...
"violate" their tenets.
An associate of mine was confined there, and has provided me with a map.
It would be difficult to get in by way of the main gate, but there is another option.
The mines break the surface of a hill south of the quarry.
I'll drop into the mines and head for the prison,
which will be found somewhere uphill and to the north.
The Hammers don't venture into these lower mine levels
because they're reputed to be haunted.
I'd rather not have to do this job,
but Cutty's a reliable fence,
and I don't appreciate the Hammerites abducting him.
And he owes me money for the Bafford job.