...And the manfools piled rock on rocks and raised a treesie roof,
hammers saws tear the skin of goodsie wood...
..and laughs at the Woodsie Lord.
...And when learns the Lord of this, He sends His beastesses to the manfools....
...who attacks and hammers saws their use-less fleshes,
and build him a house of they rotting skins.
-- Unattributed Trickster song
I was pissed at Cutty for a good while after the...
...prison debacle.
But hey, you can't blame him for what the Hammers did to him.
So I decided to go after that horn Felix talked about.
Not like I had a whole lot of choice, really...
...the rent is due...
and my landlord's even tougher than the Hammers.
The map's pretty specific about where the entrance is.
Too bad it's not as clear about where the Horn is.
Felix did some scrounging before he left,
and his notes say the horn is in the tomb of some nobles...
...the Quintus family.
Guess I'll just have to explore.
Felix, always helpful, also said that the catacombs
are supposed to be haunted.
Think I'll go make some inquiries about
where a heretic like me can get some holy water.
Always go prepared.