The ancient corruption was again contained.
To do more would have upset the balance,
but we knew to remain ever vigilant lest it resurface.
Neither the Hammers nor the pagans could be trusted not to meddle.
-- Keeper Annals
I had some money to spare after disposing of the Horn,
so it seemed time to invest in some new...
...tools.
Farkus is one of the few merchants willing to risk
selling to an independent like me,
and his prices are steep...
but the other choice is to let one of the so-called
"City Wardens" give me orders...
...And take a cut of my profits.
They'd been after me for years to
join one of their stables, but I'm not interested.
Maybe they'll get the idea and give up.
More likely they'll just ramp up the threats.
Nothing I can't handle if I'm careful.
And lucky.
And my luck seems to have finally turned for the better.