Builds your roofs of dead wood.
Builds your walls of dead stone.
Builds your dreams of dead thoughts.
Comes crying laughing singing back to life,
takes what you steal,
and pulls the skins from your dead bones shrieking.
-- Clay tablet in an abandoned Trickster temple
I was contacted by a woman named Viktoria.
She claims to represent a client who was impressed
by the way I took care of Ramirez,
and now wants me to steal something for him.
The target is a magical sword,
owned by a nobleman and collector named Constantine..
Little is known about Constantine
except that he is an eccentric new face in this city,
and mostly keeps to himself.
Viktoria says the sword will probably be on display,
but it will be well protected by guards and security systems.
She also mentioned that the guards are tough and organized,
and the mansion is confusing to navigate in.
The house was constructed recently,
so I've had to piece together my own map
from observation and hearsay.
Sounds like the place is a bit of a maze.
I guess if you're rich enough
you can build any sort of madhouse to live in.
This is going to be a challenging job,
but it will pay better than the last few I've taken.
As usual, the front entrance is heavily guarded,
but I've managed to find another way in.
'Course once I've picked up the sword
I'll still have to worry about getting back out.