Come the time of peril, did the ground gape,
and did the dead rest unquiet 'gainst us.
Our bands of iron and hammers of stone prevailed not,
and some did doubt the Builder's plan.
But the seals held strong, and the few did triumph,
and the doubters were lain into the foundations of the new sanctum.
-- Collected letters of the smith-in-exile.
The Eye that Constantine wants
is in the abandoned cathedral of the Hammerites.
The cathedral is located in the section of the city
that was deserted years ago, after some kind of catastrophe.
I've heard stories of the incident,
most are wild rumours about hordes of zombies
and raging fires.
Now that part of the city is walled off,
no one's allowed to go in.
Not that many people would dare to in the first place.
Maps of the area are easy to find,
in attics, and old trunks, but like all of them,
the one I've got is over fifty years old.
I'll make my way through the ruins to the Hammerite cathedral,
and find a way inside.
Once I get inside the cathedral, I'll have to locate The Eye.
Something tells me that this is not going to be easy.
But for the amount I'm getting paid,
I'm willing to take some serious risks.