The knowledge of those who came before could neither be disseminated or destroyed.
Its power would be a dangerous tool in the wrong hands,
but would also insure against future cataclysm.
At that time we chose to maintain it with writings preserved in extant locations.
-- Keeper Annals
The Keepers have hidden the Talisman of Fire
in a place they call "The Lost City".
Some kind of cataclysm buried the place underground ages ago.
The Keepers have sealed the access to the city,
a cleft in the river bottom near the east side.
If the materials in the library are right,
the strange stone I found can be used to open that seal.
I've also got a map,
it's so old the edges crumble in my hands.
It shows the city, or at least how it was back then.
I hope the old place hasn't changed much.