And he did say, "Shall we not use this power, as our enemies used it unto us?
Do we not carve their wild forests into our beams and boards?
Do we not tame their raging streams to carry our boats?"
And in their youth and fool- ishness, did his brothers say, "Yes, let us."
-- Collected letters of the smith-in-exile
With the Talismans, I'll be able to break the wards on the Cathedral.
It's time for me to retrieve "The Eye" and bring it to Constantine.
Last time I was here, "The Eye" was inside, in plain sight on the main altar.
I just have to grab it, and leave.
But that won't necessarily be easy if the place is as
haunted as it looked before.
So if things get tough, there is another way out,
throught the gate in the Cloister, behind the Cathedral.
The sooner this ordeal is over with, the better.
When I get paid for this job, I'm gonna retire in style.