Danced we in joys and triumphs.
With us the Woodsie Lord danced the stringsie foolsie man
Rose the storms in shouty glee, the darkness in feary glooms, the fires in happy greed.
Danced we away, and fed the sad stringsie man- fool to their devourings for our thanks.
-- Final fragment of the "Notyets" manuscript
- This way?
- Look here. Our path is true.
- In here?
- Yes.
- Since you left us, you've been a stone rolling downhill.
Now you must aim this remarkable momentum.
It is past time for the balance to shift.
- They come.
- Wha--? Wait!
- The Trickster will not forgive you for doing what he could not.
Nor, I trust, will you forgive us.
- Keepers.
Looks like I'd better get moving,
or whatever those things are will waste a perfectly good rescue.