The stone cannot know why the chisel cleaves it;
the iron cannot know why the fire scorches it.
When thy life is cleft and scorched,
when death and despair leap at thee,
beat not thy breast and curse thy evil fate,
but thank the Builder for the trials that shape thee.
-- The Hammer Book of Tenets
This was not the way things were supposed to go.
Constantine has the Eye...and my eye...
and I doubt he has anything wholesome planned for it.
The Trickster is real after all.
I don't think anyone but those crazy Hammers
really believed in the old gods.
Those crazy Hammers.
You know, it wouldn't hurt to have a few dozen
heavily-armed fanatics on MY side just about now.
If I drop by their temple and explain things,
maybe they'll be so distracted by the Trickster's return
that they'll forget to hold a grudge.
And even if they don't,
I know how to get out of Cragscleft prison already.