In the beginning we lived as thieves,
Stealing fur and fang of beasts for survival
Then came the Builder who brought us the Hammer,
And with it we forged a new way of life.
To reject the Hammer is to denounce the Builder.
-- The Hammer Book of Tenets
I was going to pay Lord Randall and his vase collection a visit,
but the Downwind Thieves' Guild beat me to the score.
Word is that they haven't divvied the booty yet.
Apparently their leaders...Donal and Reuben...
...are arguing over the prized sapphire vase.
Sounds like they could use a third party
to settle their disagreement.
Since I'm no mediator, I'll just steal the vase from them.
They'll be so busy blaming each other
no one will suspect an outsider.
The Downwinders run a gambling den called the "Overlord's Fancy,"
which operates under a nearby restaurant.
The guild's hideout is beneath the casino.
I have a rough map of the complex I got from...
..sources from the inside.
Once I'm in the Overlord's Fancy
I'll have to search for the secret entrance to the hideout.
Have to be careful, the Downwinder's know me all too well.
If they catch sight of me they'll know who took the vase.
Assuming they don't just kill me for trespassing.
Finding the vase may prove difficult,
since I have no idea where it is.
Should be a hot topic of conversation among the Downwinders.
Maybe I'll be lucky enough to overhear where they're stashing it.
Time to make a living.