From unknown origins they came
They live isolated beyond the city
The extent of their arcane power is unknown
We must be very cautious in dealing with them
Close observation must continue
-- Keeper Xavier, Treatise on Mages
The Talisman of Earth is guarded by a foreign mages' sect
known as the "Hand Brotherhood".
They reside in a compound of huge towers,
where they practice their arts of
Earth, Air, Fire, and Water.
The Talisman is likely kept in the Earth tower,
but there's little chance it'll be that simple.
No doubt the Talisman is heavily guarded
and probably protected by magic.
But mages love to write everything down...
I should "stumble" on something useful about their precious trinket.
I bribed some servants to get me a map of the common grounds...
...the best I could do since only the mages are allowed in the towers.
I'll enter the courtyard just outside the central keep entrance.
Once inside I'll need to move quickly to find the Talisman.
I wouldn't last long in a fight against the mages.