Blindness is the manfools
theys gathers up treasures and greeders themselves on gold rocks and fetters
The Woodsie One wreaks thems with lilacs and nettles
and gathers theys bones for His porridge and feathers.
-- Text Unattributed, Sumac on Parchment
The Keepers stashed the Talisman of Water
in a series of hidden caverns located deep below the city.
According to their map I'll find it in a shrine
located in the lowest cavern.
I don't expect to run into anything too threatening
other than a few venemous spiders,
however the map does contain this note:
"Stand not against us, lest you feel
the sting of ignorance's barbs."
Heh...sounds like Keeper talk for "We've rigged the place".
An informant of mine, Giry, made a home for himself in these caverns
after he lost his job tending the ticket counter
of a nearby opera house.
He should know these caverns better than anyone,
so I'll pay him a visit, to see if he has any useful information for me.