- Garrett? It's Viktoria.
I trust you made it back alive?
You've done well, Garrett. Come with me, and bring the sword.
There is someone you have to meet. It's time for the payment you've been promised.
- Yes.
- A refreshment, Mister Garrett?
I'm in the possession of a superior
brandy, that has the most...
..."restorative" effect.
- I prefer my payment in cash, not liquor, Mister...ahh...
- My apologies.
I've been watching you, Mister Garrett. So closely, in fact,
that I'm afraid I'd forgotten we haven't actually met yet.
I am...Constantine.
- All this time I thought you were going to pay me.
You've brought me here to kill me?
- But you have it all wrong, Mister Garrett.
Would it surprise you to know that it was I who hired you to steal my own sword?
Yes. You see, Viktoria and I are...
- Old associates.
- Yes. You were being tested. Do you understand?
And I must say, you more than live up to your reputation.
You are quite an extraordinary thief.
- Testing me? What is it you want from me, Constantine?
- I am a collector, Mister Garrett. But there are some 'items',
that are not available for purchase.
They must be acquired using other means.
In this case the item in question would be best acquired by thieving.
Not simple thieving...no. I need an artist. Like yourself.
- What exactly IS this...item?
- It is the gemstone called The Eye, for it's unusual...
- Appearance.
- Yes. Kept hidden in the sealed cathedral
deep inside the halls of the scum Hammerites.
Oh, but forgive me, you are, possibly,
'friendly' with the Order of the Hammer?
- No. Fanatics make unreliable friends.
- Excellent. I am prepared to offer you quite a sum.
A hundred thousand, upon receipt of The Eye.
- I don't see how I can refuse such an offer.
- Marvelous. Viktoria can fill you in on all the particulars.
And Mister Garrett...the sword. Keep it.
You have earned it. But also...
...I believe you'll find it useful in your quest.