- I can't tell you how pleased I am with you, Mister Garrett.
I simply can't find the words.
But perhaps Viktoria can help me in that regard.
She has such a way with them.
- Yes, we are both so very pleased.
- Viktoria?
- Even though The Eye is...defective.
- What?!?
- Viktoria is quite right, Mister Garrett.
I don't mean to sound ungrateful, but this eye is completely blind..
- It's a rock. It's what you asked for. Am I gonna get paid or not?
- Of course.
- Viktoria, are you prepared to give Mister Garrett his...
...Compensation?
- Bow to the Woodsie Lord and offer up your flesheye
so that his Eye of Stone may see, Manfool!
Bids he then the spruces to singer him an anthems!
And the Woodsie Lord binders them fleshes to stone!
- Did you think those ancient phrases were mere words, Manfool?
Look at me!
I am The Woodsie Lord, The Trickster of legend!
If you be thirsty, fleshthing, drink of me.
If you be hungry, then feed for I am the honeymaker, and the jacksberry!
- He am the leaf that feeders on the fleshed ones.
Thems that calls themselves Builders and wielded up a hammers against him!
- My poor Mister Garrett, you will not live to see the sprawling glory of it!
- Your sacrifice is not yet complete!
Mine lilacs and mine thistleaids must feeds, and I?
Stands He then in the greens and festered Maw
and speeds He out his judgements upon the weeps and writhing manfools!