- Pft, Keepers.
- So you think you've won.
- I think I've got my eye back..
- Yet, still, you are blind.
- If you hadn't noticed, I just saved the world. Yourself included.
- As we knew you would. As it had to be.
- Now I remember why I left the Keepers.
- And I remember why we let you go.
- What do you want from me?
You come to congratulate me?
Welcome me back to the fold?
- Very well. I will speak my piece plainly.
You have accomplished that which was written, and yes,
you've done it well.
But there is no place for you with us any longer.
Yet you will have a great need of us, and soon.
- I don't think so. I'm through with heroics.
And with your kind as well.
- You cannot run from life as you did from us, Garrett.
Life has a way of finding you.
No matter how artistic a sneak you are.
Listen, there is a book that you were not made aware of.
I'm here to tell you that it would be wise for you to read it now,
if you can still read hieroglyphs.
- I do try to forget, but you Keepers leave them everywhere for me.
- Yes. You have more friends than you know.
- Tell my friends that I don't need their secret book.
Or their glyph warnings, or
their messengers.
Tell them I'm through. Tell them it's over.
Tell them Garrett is done.
- I will tell them this:
Nothing is changed,
all is as it was written,
the Trickster is dead, beware the dawn of...
...the Metal Age.